Evyatar Haim

Full Stack Developer

A full Stack Developer, focused on JavaScript Technologies across the whole stack (MongoDB, SQL, Express, React, Node.js, Unity, C#). Experienced in building complete web applications with backend API's. Formerly a sound engineer & musician with specialization in recording studios.

evyataros1@gmail.com

+972-05-09098806 Tel Aviv-Yafo, Israel

https://github.com/evyatarhaim1

www.linkedin.com/in/evyatar-haim in

https://evyatarhaim1.github.io/portfolio.github.io/



Technical skills

Client: JavaScript (ES5/6), jQuery, HTML, CSS,

Materialize

Server + DBs: Node.js, Express, MongoDB,

Mongoose, SQL, Unity, C#.

Frameworks: React, Mobx, React Native, Redux. **Tools:** Object-Oriented Programming, Git, working in collaboration in Github, Heroku, Wordpress, Python.

Work Experience

Seller - Guitar Department. Kley Zemer. Tel Aviv, Israel. 2016 - 2017.

Full acquaintance with a variety of musical instruments, adjusting the musical instruments suitable for customers. Mixer calibration, set-up of microphones.

Sound Engineer & Recording Studio Technician. Kicha Studios. Tel Aviv, Israel. 2015 - 2016. Mixer calibration, set-up of microphones. Signal-flow preparations according to specifications. Ongoing work with ProTools and analog console.

Album recording for A-wa, Shuli Rand, Ehud Banai, Jane Bordeaux, Shlomi Shaban, and more.

Sound Engineer & Producer. A-WA band. Tel Aviv, Israel. 2012 – 2015.

Assistant Technician in the production of A-WA's debut album. Responsible for all guides and initial sketches. Guitar player.

Military Service

Operations

2006-2009 | Ovda Base | CID Metzah Unit | Operations Room NCO

Management of the operations room routine and ongoing work with the base commander and detective staff. Responsible for the "Arava Dromit" sector. Received the unit's excellence certificate for 2009.

Education

Full Stack Web Developer

Elevation Academy

2019-2020 | Tel Aviv, Israel | Graduated | Course Page An industry-based intensive 3-month 480hs coding bootcamp which covered the entire MERN stack and beyond. Built a number of end-to-end projects from scratch while adhering to solid object-oriented programming principles and communicating with a number of external APIs.

Sound Engineer Kinneret Academy 2009-2011 | Kinneret, Israel | Graduated

Languages

English •••

Hebrew

Spanish

